<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="pickup_lines">
		<item> You must be in a wrong place - the Miss Universe contest is over there.  </item>
		<item> Did you fart? Because you blew me away </item>
		<item> Was that an earthquake or did u just rock my world?  </item>
		<item> I may not be a genie but I can make your dreams come true </item>
		<item> Are you a magnet cuz im attracted to you </item>
		<item> Does this rag smell like chloroform to you?  </item>
		<item> I wish you were DSL so I could get high-speed access.  </item>
		<item> I know its not Christmas, but Santa's lap is always ready.  </item>
		<item> Baby your like a student and I am like a math book, you solve all my problems </item>
		<item> "Why does it feel like the most beautiful girl in the world is in this room?" </item>
		<item> Can I take a picture of you, so I can show Santa just what I want for Christmas.  </item>
		<item> Do you have any raisins? No? How about a date?  </item>
		<item> I was blinded by your beauty so I'm going to need your name and number for insurance reasons.  </item>
		<item> I'm sorry, were you talking to me? Her: No. Well then, please start.  </item>
		<item> I know I dont have a chance, but I just wanted to hear an angel talk.  </item>
		<item> Roses are red, violets are blue, how would you like it if I came home with you?  </item>
		<item> Hey I just realized this, but you look alot like my next girlfriend.  </item>
		<item> Are your legs tired, because you've been running through my mind all day long.  </item>
		<item> Are you lost? Because heaven's a long way from here.  </item>
		<item> POOF! (What are u doing?) I'm here, where are your other two wishes?  </item>
		<item> I hope you know CPR, because you take my breath away.  </item>
		<item> Girl, you better have a license, cuz you are driving me crazy!  </item>
		<item> If you were the new burger at McDonalds you would be the Mcgorgeous!  </item>
		<item> Do you have the time? (she gives you the time) No, the time to write my number down .  </item>
		<item> Let's make like a fabric softener and snuggle.  </item>
		<item> Are you an interior decorator? When I saw you the room became beautiful.  </item>
		<item> Hello, I'm a thief, and I'm here to steal your heart.  </item>
		<item> Is that top felt? [No] Would you like it to be?  </item>
		<item> Apart from being sexy, what do you do for a living?  </item>
		<item> Is your last name Gillete cause your the best a man can get.  </item>
		<item> Are you a parking ticket? (What?) You got fine written all over you.  </item>
		<item> I'm invisible. (Really?) Can you see me? (Yes) How about tomorrow night?  </item>
		<item> You can fall off a building, you can fall out a tree, but baby, the best way to fall is in love with me.  </item>
		<item> I have never had a dream come true until the day that I met you.  </item>
		<item> You look life my first wife! (how many have you had?) none.  </item>
		<item> Do you have a sunburn, or are you always this hot?  </item>
		<item> I'm addicted to yes, and I'm allergic to no. So what's it gonna be?  </item>
		<item> If I could rearrange the alphabet, I'd put U and I together.  </item>
		<item> Turn to the girl sitting next to you at the bar and say... "I'm not really this tall....I'm sitting on my wallet." </item>
		<item> This is a test of the emergency pickup line service. Beeeeeeeeeep. If you had been any less beautiful, you would have just heard a bad pickup line.  </item>
		<item> If this bar is a meat market, you must be the prime rib.  </item>
		<item> I know I'm not a grocery item but I can tell when you're checking me out.  </item>
		<item> If beauty were sunlight, you'd shine from a million light-years away.  </item>
		<item> Do you mind if I hang out here until its safe back where I farted.  </item>
		<item> Life without you would be like a broken pencil...pointless.  </item>
		<item> Your body is a wonderland and i want to be Alice.  </item>
		<item> I'm like chocolate pudding, I look like crap but im as sweet as can be.  </item>
		<item> Can I have directions? ["To where?"] To your heart.  </item>
		<item> Are you an alien? because you just abducted my heart.  </item>
		<item> Did you fart, 'cause you blow me away!  </item>
		<item> I hope there's a fireman around, cause you're smokin'!  </item>
		<item> If you were a booger I'd pick you first.  </item>
		<item> Excuse me, I think you have something in your eye. Nope, it's just a sparkle.  </item>
		<item> You've been a bad girl/boy. Go to my room.  </item>
		<item> If beauty were time, you'd be an eternity.  </item>
		<item> Do you know karate? 'Cause your body is really kickin'.  </item>
		<item> Are you as beautiful on the inside as you are on the outside?  </item>
		<item> Like the sheets on your bed I want cover you with love.  </item>
		<item> Do you have a Bandaid? Because I just scraped my knee falling for you.  </item>
		<item> Hi, I just wanted to give you the satisfaction of turning me down; go ahead say no.  </item>
		<item> I hope your day is as radiant as your smile.  </item>
		<item> You make me melt like hot fudge on a sundae.  </item>
		<item> You know what? Your eyes are the same color as my Porsche.  </item>
		<item> Are you an alien?, because you just abducted my heart.  </item>
		<item> What has 142 teeth and holds back the incredible hulk? My zipper.  </item>
		<item> I can tell your future, it is you giving me your number.  </item>
		<item> Hi, I'm Mr. Right. Someone said you were looking for me.  </item>
		<item> Giant polar bear (What?) It's an icebreaker. Hi, my name is....  </item>
		<item> Your so hot when i look at you I get a tan </item>
		<item> I must be a snowflake, 'cuz I've fallen for you.  </item>
		<item> You look so sweet your givin me a toothache.  </item>
		<item> My love for you is like the universe...neverending!!  </item>
		<item> If looks could kill you would be a weapon of mass destruction.  </item>
		<item> You - "Did it hurt". The other person will naturally say "Did what hurt?", You - "When you fell from heaven." </item>
		<item> Excuse me, can you empty your pockets? I believe you have stolen my heart.  </item>
		<item> Do you have a map? Because I just keep getting lost in your eyes!  </item>
		<item> You say "I bet you $20 I can kiss you without using my lips." She says, "Bet's on." You kiss her then say, "I lost." </item>
		<item> You got something on your chest: my eyes </item>
		<item> Do you believe in the hereafter? Well, then I guess you know what I'm here after.  </item>
		<item> I don't know if you're beautiful or not, I haven't gotten past your eyes yet.  </item>
		<item> What does it feel like to be the most beautiful girl in this room?  </item>
		<item> Your eyes are as blue as my toilet water at home.  </item>
		<item> I'm not drunk, I'm just intoxicated by you.  </item>
		<item> Do you want to make millions? millions of babies!  </item>
		<item> The night is young, the moon is bright, and you are here with me tonight.  </item>
		<item> I wanna bag you like some groceries.  </item>
		<item> kiss me if I am wrong, but isn't your name (take a guess)...Janice????  </item>
		<item> Are you from Tennessee? Cause you're the only TEN I see </item>
	</string-array>
</resources>
